<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on NakSquad</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on NakSquad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Untitled. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NAK#1 Altis Invade and Annex</title>
      <link>/servers/nak1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 01:32:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/servers/nak1/</guid>
      <description>See the main server for server description and rules
Mods    When Event Required Mods Optional Mods HTML Tool Last Updated      Vanilla x Huge Allowed Mods List x 08-30-2023   Fri@9pm Assault and Pepper x Huge Allowed Mods List &amp;gt;NAK Modset Manager&amp;lt; 08-30-2023    Events Assault and Pepper, Combined Operations  Friday @ 9pm Eastern/US Runs late into the night, until we run out of players  Required Mods for event  Any allowed mods  Event rules  If you are joining the event you must be in the event channel in teamspeak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAK#2 Public Modded Zeus</title>
      <link>/servers/nak2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/servers/nak2/</guid>
      <description>See the main server for server description and rules
Please complete the Zeus Survey for every zeus mission to take part in. It helps to improve the quality of the missions and the enjoyment of the servers for everyone.
This server has required mods.
Mods    When Event Required Mods Required Event Mods Optional Mods HTML Tool Last Updated     Old Unsung Collection na Collection NAK Modset Manager 07-22-2023   Base Base Collection na Collection NAK Modset Manager 08-26-2023   Current&amp;ndash;&amp;gt; Halloweed Collection Halloween Collection &amp;gt;NAK Modset Manager&amp;lt; 10-28-2023    Events NakTac  Event Days and Time to be Determined  Required Mods for event  Required Mods for event TBD Test mods  Event rules  There are special rules for this event There are qualifications to join the unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAK#3 Tanoa Quicksilver</title>
      <link>/servers/nak3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 01:32:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/servers/nak3/</guid>
      <description>See the main server for server description and rules
Mods    When Event Required Mods Optional Mods HTML Tool Last Updated      Vanilla x Huge Allowed Mods List x 08-30-2023   Tue@7pm Tanoa Tac Tuesday x Huge Allowed Mods List &amp;gt;NAK Modset Manager&amp;lt; 08-30-2023    Events Tactical Tuesday  Tuesdays @ 7pm Eastern/US Runs until server restart at 9pm  Required Mods for event  Any allowed mods Please do not run RHS as it breaks sound for others on this server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAK#4 Public Vanilla Zeus</title>
      <link>/servers/nak4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 01:32:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/servers/nak4/</guid>
      <description>See the main server for server description and rules
When joining from the launcher click the &amp;ldquo;Keep Current Loaded Mods&amp;rdquo; button not the top one.
Please complete the Zeus Survey for every zeus mission to take part in. It helps to improve the quality of the missions and the enjoyment of the servers for everyone.
Mods    When Event Required Mods Optional Mods HTML Tool Last Updated     Wed@7pm BirdOps x Huge Allowed Mods List &amp;gt;NAK Modset Manager&amp;lt; 08-30-2023   Sat@5pm NakOps x see modset manager &amp;gt;NAK Modset Manager&amp;lt; 08-30-2023    Vanilla x Huge Allowed Mods List x 08-30-2023    Events NAK Ops  Saturday @ 5pm Eastern/US Runs 2-3 hours depending on the size and complexity of the mission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tactical Operations General Info</title>
      <link>/naktac/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naktac/general/</guid>
      <description>Some of the things you can expect.
Voice Communication  Your microphone must be well adjusted and you must be able to communicate clearly. If you are in an environment with a lot of background noise, you may be required to use push-to-talk. Your microphone should only be transmitting your voice and only when intended. IRL conversations and other loud and/or unexpected noises are distracting to both the basic immersion of the mission and to communication itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Operating Procedures</title>
      <link>/naktac/sop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naktac/sop/</guid>
      <description>While there may be specific training for certain procedures, much of what you need to know can be found as a standard operating procedure here. We prefer that most knowledge starts with SOPs and is perfected and enhanced with training and experience rather than solely through training and experience.
We cover these the four basic roles in this SOP guide because nine times out of ten, a player is going to find himself in one of these roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Type-1 Battle Drills</title>
      <link>/naktac/drills/type-1-drills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naktac/drills/type-1-drills/</guid>
      <description>Battle Drill 1: Conducting an Assault  Battle Drill 1 is a simple offensive plan, with our side firing the first shot. The most planned battle drill is a simple assault or flanking assault. Nearly all assault plans are based off the guiding principle that once the assault begins, there is no fire without movement and there is no movement without fire. Violent action alone does not take ground in a meaningful way and neither does moving through it without dominating that territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battle Drills</title>
      <link>/naktac/battledrills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naktac/battledrills/</guid>
      <description>The idea behind a &amp;ldquo;battle drill&amp;rdquo; is that it is a standardized way to react to a common battlefield event. Battle drills ensure that everyone is on the same page of music, so to speak, and allows for a rapid reaction to an event with the minimum of orders needing to be issued.
Understand that simple drills and clear commands will have a disproportionate effect on outcomes. Effective battle drills will mean you have an instant PLAN which can be immediately modified by the tactical leader as necessary for the situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Type-2 Battle Drills</title>
      <link>/naktac/drills/type-2-drills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naktac/drills/type-2-drills/</guid>
      <description>Battle Drill 2: Reaction to Contact / Reaction to Enemy Fire  Battle Drill 2 is nearly identical, however the enemy initiated the firefight.  The most fundamental battle drill is reacting to enemy fire. It forms the basis for many of the other tactics covered in this guide, and these guidelines should be kept in mind when reading about them and applied as necessary.
General Fundamental Principles  React immediately  Return fire Communicate Seek cover All at the same time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAK#n SnyOps</title>
      <link>/servers/nakn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 01:32:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/servers/nakn/</guid>
      <description>Who let you in here? How do you know about this place? SECURITY!\  This server is completely experimental and is subject to change at any time.
However, this does not mean there are no rules.
See the main server for server description and rules This is where I will be testing new mods and missions.
Mods    When Event Required Mods Optional Mods HTML Tool Last Updated     Current&amp;ndash;&amp;gt; Base Collection Collection &amp;gt;NAK Modset Manager&amp;lt; 08-26-2023    HTML</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mod Tool</title>
      <link>/posts/230830-newmodtool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/230830-newmodtool/</guid>
      <description>NAK has a new Modset Tool that allows the Servers and Events team to update mods without having to manually generate and distribute PRESET HTML files. This will allow for faster updates and more accurate mod pack information.
 To use, select Server Info from the SnyOps main page and click on the server you want to get the mod list for. Click on the Nak Modset Manager link. Select the Optional mods you want to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New HTMLs</title>
      <link>/posts/230806-newhtmls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/230806-newhtmls/</guid>
      <description>New Sny Recommended HTMLs uploaded for all servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Site</title>
      <link>/posts/230806-newsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/230806-newsite/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new server info site.
This will contain both information and news about the Nak servers, events, mods and highlight and link to any changes that relate to using Nak servers.
If you see anything broken please let me know,
 Sny  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
