<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NakTac on NakSquad</title>
    <link>/naktac/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NakTac on NakSquad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Untitled. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/naktac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tactical Operations General Info</title>
      <link>/naktac/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naktac/general/</guid>
      <description>Some of the things you can expect.
Voice Communication  Your microphone must be well adjusted and you must be able to communicate clearly. If you are in an environment with a lot of background noise, you may be required to use push-to-talk. Your microphone should only be transmitting your voice and only when intended. IRL conversations and other loud and/or unexpected noises are distracting to both the basic immersion of the mission and to communication itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Operating Procedures</title>
      <link>/naktac/sop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naktac/sop/</guid>
      <description>While there may be specific training for certain procedures, much of what you need to know can be found as a standard operating procedure here. We prefer that most knowledge starts with SOPs and is perfected and enhanced with training and experience rather than solely through training and experience.
We cover these the four basic roles in this SOP guide because nine times out of ten, a player is going to find himself in one of these roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battle Drills</title>
      <link>/naktac/battledrills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naktac/battledrills/</guid>
      <description>The idea behind a &amp;ldquo;battle drill&amp;rdquo; is that it is a standardized way to react to a common battlefield event. Battle drills ensure that everyone is on the same page of music, so to speak, and allows for a rapid reaction to an event with the minimum of orders needing to be issued.
Understand that simple drills and clear commands will have a disproportionate effect on outcomes. Effective battle drills will mean you have an instant PLAN which can be immediately modified by the tactical leader as necessary for the situation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
